The final frontier...and beyond.
Star Trek Beyond is a action, adventure, science
fiction film directed by Justin Lin.
The USS Enterprise crew explores the furthest reaches of uncharted space, where they encounter a
mysterious new enemy who puts them and everything the Federation stands for to the test.
Captain James T. Kirk, played by Chris Pine.
Commander Spock, played by Zachary Quinto.
Dr. Leonard 'Bones' McCoy, played by Karl Urban.
Lieutenant Nyota Uhura, played by Zoe Saldaña.
Lieutenant Commander Montgomery 'Scotty' Scott, played by Simon Pegg.
Lieutenant Hikaru Sulu, played by John Cho.
Star Trek Beyond is a 2016 American science fiction action film directed
by Justin Lin, and written by Simon Pegg and Doug Jung.
It is the 13th film in the Star Trek franchise and the third installment in the reboot
series, following Star Trek (2009) and Star Trek Into Darkness (2013).
Chris Pine and Zachary Quinto reprise their respective roles as Captain James T.
Kirk and Commander Spock, with Pegg, Karl Urban, Zoe Saldaña, John Cho, and
Anton Yelchin reprising their roles from the previous films.
Idris Elba, Sofia Boutella, Joe Taslim, and Lydia Wilson also appear.
Principal photography began in Vancouver on June 25, 2015.
Two weeks after its Sydney premiere, it was released in the United
States on July 22, 2016, by Paramount Pictures.
The film is dedicated to the memory of Yelchin and actor Leonard
Nimoy, who both died before the film was released.
The film grossed $343.5 million at the box office, and
received positive reviews from critics.
At the 89th Academy Awards, the film was nominated
for Best Makeup and Hairstyling.
A sequel entered development but was ultimately canceled.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, sequel, stranded, hatred, lgbt.
The tone is thought_provoking.